justarticles.com 2007-12-11

# Web Content, Keyword Articles, Blog Design, SEO and Copywriting Services

**Just Articles Privacy Policy ...**  

Just Articles will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us in the quote or order form. 

No personally identifiable information is exchanged with any outside parties, read more below.

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page of our web site

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Just Articles web site. On the contact information page you can submit a request for more information, free quote or an initial consultation. The types of personal information collected on this page is: 

Name   
E-mail Address   
Phone Number 

When you visit the Just Articles web site, like when you visit most other web sites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the Internet (such as “google.com” or “yahoo.com”), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at the Just Articles web site, and the Internet address of the web site, if any, from which you linked directly to the Just Articles web site. This information is not personally identifiable. 

**How We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when submitting an information request. We do not share this information with outside parties. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We use the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by our servers primarily to help us administer and improve our web site. We may also use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Please direct any "privacy policy" questions to Just Articles per the 

contact page for Review and Response, Thank You
